Baruch, Ismar Compilation of U.S. Employment Service and U.S. Civil Service Documents 6099
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Employment Management in Industry., 1918-1932 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  v.1. Bulletins, clippings, pamphlets, reports.
- Employment Management in Industry., 1920-1938 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  v.2. Bulletins, clippings, pamphlets, reports.
- Employment Management in Industry., 1929-1939 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  v.3. Bulletins, clippings, pamphlets, reports. Spine Title: Employment Management.
- Employment Management in Industry., 1925-1932 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  v.4. Spine title: Pamphlets re Employment Management.
- Employment Management in Industry., 1921-1941 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  v.5. Bulletins, clippings, pamphlets, reports.
- Employment Management in Industry., 1922-1934 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  v.6. Bulletins, clippings, pamphlets, reports.
- Employment Management in Industry., 1919-1942 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  v.7. Bulletins, clippings, pamphlets, reports.
- Industrial Safety, 1949-1950 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  no.130-137. President's Conference on Industrial Safety, Bureau of Labor Statistics Bulletins.
- Wage Survey Reports., 1929-1931 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  v.1. State, local, and industrial
- Wage Survey Reports., 193101936 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  v.2. State, local, and industrial
- Administrative Bulletin., 1931-1932 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  Publication devoted to the business and personnel activities of the U.S. Department of Agriculture.
- Miscellaneous Wage Data., 1923-1944 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  v.4. State, local, and industrial
- Miscellaneous Wage Data., 1924-1944 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  v.5. State, local, and industrial
- U.S. Employment Service. Miscellaneous Papers., 1934-1936 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  v.1. Includes "Professional training for the field of public employment office work."
- U.S. Employment Service. Miscellaneous Papers., 1937 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  v.2. Includes "Professional training for the field of public employment office work."
- Wage Bulletins., 1935-1944 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Wage Bulletins., 1940-1945 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Wage Bulletins., 1944-1945 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Wage Bulletins., 1945-1947 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Wage Bulletins., 1947-1948 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Wage Survey Reports., 1923-1937 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  v.3. State, local, and industrial
- Pay Stabilization., 1942 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  v.1. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- U.S. Employment Service. Cotton Textile Industry., 1935 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- U.S. Employment Service. Occupational Research Program., 1934-1935 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- U.S. Employment Service. Occupational Research Program., 1935-1936 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- U.S. Employment Service. Occupational Research Program., 1936 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- U.S. Employment Service. Occupational Research Program., 1936-1937 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- U.S. Employment Service. Occupational Research Program., 1936-1940 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Wages and Hours in Industry., 1936 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  v.1. National Recovery Administration source material by Solomon Barkin and Anne Page.
- Wages and Hours in Industry., 1936 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  v.2. National Recovery Administration source material by Solomon Barkin and Anne Page.
- Wages and Hours in Industry., 1936 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  v.3. National Recovery Administration source material by Solomon Barkin and Anne Page.
- Pay Stabilization., 1942-1943 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  v.2. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Pay Stabilization., 1943 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  v.3. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Pay Stabilization., 1943 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  v.4. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Pay Stabilization., 1943 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  v.5. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Pay Stabilization., 1943 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  v.6. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Pay Stabilization., 1943 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  v.7. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Pay Stabilization., 1943 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  v.8. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Pay Stabilization., 1944 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  v.9. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Pay Stabilization., 1943-1944 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  v.10. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Pay Stabilization., 1944-1945 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  v.11. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Pay Stabilization., 1943-1945 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  v.12. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Pay Stabilization., 1942-1945 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  v.13. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Pay Stabilization., 1943-1947 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  v.14. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Pay Stabilization., 1945-1946 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  v.15. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Pay Stabilization., 1945 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  v.16. Manuals, regulations, and orders, by National Wage Stabilization Board, and other Federal agencies.
- Training Within Industry., 1941-1942 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  U.S. War Production Board. Bulletins, reports, and miscellaneous publications.
- Training Within Industry. Reports., 1940-1945 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- U.S. Works Progress Administration. Technical Series., 1937 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  Installation of comprehensive personnel service records. Definition of police beats. Installation of a single finger-print file. Indexing vital statistics certificates.
- Classification Book. Correspondence., 1939-1941 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Classification Book. Correspondence., 1939-1941 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Classification Book. Correspondence., 1939-1941 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Classification Book. Notes., 1939-1941 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- CSA Classification Book. First Draft., 1939-1941 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  Chapters 1-3
- CSA Classification Book. First Draft., 1939-1941 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  Chapters 4-6
- CSA Classification Book. First Draft., 1939-1941 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  Chapters 7-10
- Outlines, Articles, and Talks. (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Outlines, Articles, and Talks., 1923-1944 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Outlines, Articles, and Talks., 1928-1933 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Efficiency Ratings., 1916-1934 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Efficiency Ratings., 1921-1934 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Efficiency Ratings., 1935-1941 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Efficiency Ratings., 1924-1941 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Forest Service Training Course., 1930 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Forest Service Training Course., 1930-1931 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Personnel Administration., 1938-1940 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  v.1-2
- Personnel Administration., 1940-1942 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  v.3-4
- Personnel Administration., 1942-1943 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Personnel Administration., 1943-1944 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Position Classification Analysis., 1938 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Public Personnel Quarterly, 1939-1941 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Public Personnel Quarterly, 1941-1942 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  v.2-3
- Civil Service Commission Library Accessions., 1941-1942 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Civil Service Commission Library Accessions., 1942-1943 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Civil Service Commission Library Accessions., 1943-1944 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Civil Service Commission Library Accessions., 1944-1945 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Civil Service Observer., 1932-1933 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Civil Service Observer., 1934-1935 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Decisions of the Comptroller General re Classification., 1924-1927 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Decisions of the Comptroller General re Classification., 1928-1931 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Decisions of the Comptroller General re Classification. Digest., 1924-1927 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Efficiency Ratings., 1921-1941 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Papers and Addresses by Ismar Baruch., 1929-1946 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Administrative Procedure., 1940 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- American University Lectures., 1935 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Analysis of Positions., 1934 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Analysis of Positions., 1934 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Classification. Farm Credit Administration of Spokane., 1936 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Decisions of the Comptroller General re Classification., 1932-1934 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Decisions of the Comptroller General re Classification. Digest., 1928-1931 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Decisions of the Comptroller General re Classification. Digest., 1932-1934 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Decisions of the Comptroller General re Classification. Digest., 1935-1936 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Home Owners Loan Corporation. Specifications., 1937-1940 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Personnel Procedures Manual., 1945 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Standard Job Descriptions., 1942-1943 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Administrative Planning Manuals., 1942 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Administrative Procedure., 1941 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Classification Plan. Home Owners Loan Corporation., 1934 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Classification Plan. Home Owners Loan Corporation., 1935 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Farm Credit Administration Qualifications Statement., 1935 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Federal Personnel Laws., 1916-1934 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- History of Federal Classification., 1789-1938 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- History of Position-Classification and Salary Standardization in the Federal Service., 1798-1941 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  PCD Manual no.A-2
- History of Position-Classification and Salary Standardization in the Federal Service., 1798-1941 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  PCD Manual no.A-2. Copy 2. Includes other manuals.
- Report by the Committee on Improvements in the Merit System., 1937 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Report by the Committee on Improvements in the Merit System., 1937 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Report by the Committee on Improvements in the Merit System., 1937 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- U.S. Civil Service Commission. Correspondence and Travel Manuals., 1936 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Act of August 1, 1942 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Articles on Federal Classification., 1920-1924 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Classification. Farm Credit Administration., 1934-1935 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Facts and Falacies about Classification., 1937 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  Civil Service Assembly Pamphlet no.10
- Farm Credit Administration District Specifications., 1936 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Farm Credit Administration Districts. Minimum Qualifications., 1936 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Federal Relations to Research., 1937-1938 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  National Resources Committee study
- Fifty U.S. Civil Service Commissioners., 1971 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Groups and Their Administration., 1937 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Index to Civil Service Commission Annual Reports., 1972 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Lithographic Wage Project., 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Reallocation Prohibition., 1933-1935 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Selected Index to Civil Service Commission Annual Reports., 1962 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Veterans Bureau Field Specifications., 1928-1929 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Chamber of Commerce of the United States: HOW MANY TOO MANY?, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. Department of Government Affairs. Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Washington, DC.
- The Essentials of a Comprehensive Personnel Program, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  Fred Telford. 1930. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. Chicago, Illinois.
- In-Service Trained for the Personnel Job, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  U.S. Council of personal administration. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission
- As I See It: Observations of a Civil Servant, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  Warner W. Stockberger. May 5, 1942. Special Adviser to the Secretary United States Department of Agriculture. Washington, 1941. U.S. Civil Service Commission Library.
- Legislative Restrictions on Time Studies in the Federal Government, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  U.S. Bureau of the budget.
- The WHAT - WHY - HOW of Manpower Utilization, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. Bureau of Manpower Utilization. War Manpower Commission. Washington, DC.
- Notes on the Governmental Executive, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  Donald Crawford Stone
- Some Pointers on How to Supervise, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  U.S. Office of price administration.
- Conservation and Utilization of Manpower in the Federal Government, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  U.S. Bureau of the budget. 1951
- Report on Responsibility for Personnel Management in the Federal Service, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  Civil service assembly of the United States and Canada. National capital chapter. 1952
- The Personnel Classification Board, 1923 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  National Civil Service Reform League 1923. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission
- The Administration of a Classification Plan Through Periodic Audits, 1936 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  An example taken from the departmental service of the Federal Government by Ismar Baruch. Civil Service Assembly. Pamphlet No.5. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. September 1936.
- The Human Element in Personnel Management, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  Lawrence A. Appley. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. October 1, 1941
- American Municipal Association: Emergency Personnel Policies, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  A checklist of items which might be considered by state and local governments. The American Municipal Association Bulletin no. 142. Civil service assembly of the United States and Canada. Special Bulletin no. 14. 1940. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. Chicago, Illinois. September, 1940.
- Federal Regulations Governing Pay Increases in State and Local Public Services, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  Civil service assembly of the United States and Canada. 1942. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- Analysis of the Salary Study and Proposed Pay Adjustment Plan., 1954 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  of George Fry and Associates, Inc. Analysis by Alphonse H. Clemens. May 1954
- Excerpts from Address Before the Society for Personnel Administration, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  March 23, 1954. Edward H. Rees (R- Kansas).
- The Higher Civil Service: Needs, Proposals, Prospects, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  George A. Graham, The Brookings Institution. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- How Your Government Job is Classified, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  U.S. Department of Commerce. Office of International Trade Operations. Administrative Management Staff. Division of Personnel Management. Washington, DC. August 1946. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- Manpower Planning Activities of Public Personnel Agencies, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  Civil Service Assembly of the United States and Canada. CSA Information and Consultation Service. November 30, 1951. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- Public Dissent and the Public Employee, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  Department of Justice. Remarks by William H. Rehnquist. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. September 18, 1970
- Guidance for Evaluation of the ole of the Federal Manager in "New Federalism", 1972 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. June 28, 1972.
- Lemons and Roses; Operators View Central Staff, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  Randall B. Ripley. 1963. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- The Job of the Central Staff Agencies, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  James W. Davis, 1965. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- Draft of a Report to the President, 1911 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  on the hours of work and leaves of absence of the personnel of the executive civil service in the District of Columbia. Prepared by The Commission on Economy and Efficiency. December, 1911.
- The Story of SPA: 20 years of progress in personnel administration, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. June 6, 1957.
- Bureau of Public Personnel Administration: Its organization and work, 1926 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. April 30, 1926.
- Employee Work Productivity in the Federal Service, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  Society of Personnel Administration. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. Federal Service 1952.
- A New Emphasis in Federal Personnel, Personal, Research and Administration, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  Lawrence J. O'Rouke. 1930. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- Value of Pesonnel Research (Box 46, Folder 30)
  L.J. O'Rourke. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- Selected Public Statements on Government Mattes, By President-Elect John F. Kennedy, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  U.S. Civil Service Commission. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. 1960
- Overtime, Night, Holiday, and Sunday Pay Practices in State Governments, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  Civil Service Assembly of the U.S. & Canada. September 1950.
- Federal Civilian Employees your Unemployment Compensation, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  U.S. Department of Labor 1954.
- Standard Job Class Definitions, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  For use with the PPA periodic pay survey. Public Personnel Association. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. October 3, 1958.
- Improving Our Federal Personnel Program, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  David N. Henderson. Manpower Utilization Subcommittee, House Post Office and Civil Service Committee. Before Society for Personnel Administration. Washington, DC. January 27, 1965.
- Administrative Ability, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  Its Discovery and Development by Walter Van Dyke Bingham. Society for Personnel Administration. Pamphlet no.1. 1939
- Motion to Reconsider Calendar 21 and Statement in Support of Motion, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  President's conference on administrative procedure. 1954. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- The Government manager in 2000 A.D, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  Elmer B. Stats. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. August 22, 1967
- Federal History Program, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  U.S. President, 1945- (Harry S. Truman) 1951. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- The Administrative Process - The Third Decade, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  James McCauley Landis. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. August 29, 1960
- Pioneers in Public Administration, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  1965 edited by Troy R. Westmeyer. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- Staffing our Government for World Leadership, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  by Neil McElroy. U.S. Civil Service Commission Library. March 6, 1961
- Analysis and Evaluation of Executive Positions, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  Edward N. Hay. 1951. Management Report no. 117. Published by Research Division, California Personnel Management Association Fifth Floor, Farm Credit Bldg., 2180 Silvia Street, Berkeley 4, California.
- Controlling the Bureaucracy: Will Ses Make a Difference?, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  Toni Moarzotto, Towson State University and Carolyn Ban and Edie Goldenberg, The Office of Personnel Management. August 27, 1981. Office of Personnel Management Library.
- How Can Classification Aid in Placement, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  by W.P Lehman. Speech delivered before the Classification Section of the Society of Personnel Administration. February 12, 1941
- Conversation Hour: Evaluation and Job Analysis, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 46)
  Ernest S. Pimoff. U.S. Office of Personnel Management (retired) and Job Element Research. Paper Presented at the 1982 Convention of the American Psychological Association. August 25, 1982.
- Commemorative Hour Honoring the Late Robert J. Wherry, Sr., 1982 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  Ernest S. Primoff. U.S. Office of Personnel Management (retired) and Job Element Research. Presentation at the 1982 Convention of the American Psychological Association. August 25, 1982.
- Federal Classification Act Salary Ranges For Positions Covered in the Bureau of Labor Statistics, National Survey of Professional, Administrative, Technical, and Clerical Pay, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  U.S Bureau of the Budget. December 4, 1960. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- Professional Research Personnel Opinions and Attitudes, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 49)
  n.d. Booz, Allen & Hamilton. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. December 5, 1956.
- The Federal Scientist Administrator, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 50)
  n.d. Eugene S. Uyeki. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. January 9, 1954.
- Report of the Assembly on Scientific Personnel in Government, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 51)
  n.d. Conference on Science and Democratic Government. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission. May 1, 1962
- Personnel Procurement Costs of Selected Contactors for Recruitment of Engineering and Technical Personnel Supplied by the Department of the Navy, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 52)
  January 22, 1957. U.S. Department of the Navy. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- Personnel Management Program for Scientists and Engineers (Box 46, Folder 53)
  n.d. U.S. Department of the Air Force. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- Technical Employment in the Federal Government, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 54)
  U.S. Interdepartmental committee on scientific research and development. June 1952
- Training on Scientific Personnel in Government Service, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 55)
  U.S. Advisory committee on scientific personnel. April 1946.
- Compensating Management Jobs in Government, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 56)
  A talk before the Public Personnel Association Conference. October 26, 1960. Richard M. Paget. Library U.S. Civil Service Commission.
- Government and Outside Salary Comparisons, 1926 (Box 46, Folder 57)
  October 6, 1926.United States Department of Labor Bureau of Labor Statistics,
- Pay of Government Officials, 1932 (Box 46, Folder 58)
  U.S. Civil Service Commission Library: December 5, 1948. George Washington bicentennial celebration
- Statement Regarding Restrictions in the Hiring of Upper-Grade Employees, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 59)
  Federal Professional Association. Library U.S. Civil Services Commission. 1966.
- Graphic Chart; Federal Reclassification as Applied to District of Columbia, 1922 (Box 46, Folder 60)
  American Association of Engineers. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. 1922
- Schedule of Rates of Pay on the Silver Roll, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 61)
  Panama Canal, Executive office. 1943. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library.
- Report Comparing the Trend of Government Salaries with the Trend in the Consumers' Price Index, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 62)
  U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. 1951. by Honorable Olin D. Johnston, Chairman of the Committee n Post Office and Civil Service. United States Senate.
- Summary Report on Within-Grade and Quality Increase Features of the Salary Reform Act, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 63)
  U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. June 29, 1965.
- The Future of Classification, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 64)
  Speech Given November 19, 1954 by M. Ismar Baruch, Technical Advisor to the Civil Service Commission. Advanced Classification Seminar Conducted by Classification Branch Departmental Civilian Personnel Division Administrative Office Navy Department.
- Executives for Government - Past, Present, and Future, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 65)
  U.S. Civil Services Commission Library. John A. Perkins, President, University of Delaware. 1958.
- Making Government Work, 1935 (Box 46, Folder 66)
  Luther Gulick. 1935. U.S. Civil Services Commission Library.
- Democracy and Bureaucracy, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 67)